lift.do 2018-08-14

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy 

Effective Date: December 31, 2014. 

INTRODUCTION 

The Lift Worldwide, Inc. (“Coach.me”) websites (collectively, the “Website”), all other products and services, including mobile applications, owned, controlled or offered by Coach.me, and all content offered as part thereof, are collectively referred to herein as the “Services.” Subscribers, account holders, customers, users, and others who download, access, use, and/or subscribe to the Services (“you”) agree to the following privacy policy (the “Privacy Policy”). The Privacy Policy should serve as an accessible guide to the information we collect during your use of the Services. By using the Services, you agree to this Privacy Policy, and you represent that you are over 13 years of age. 

COLLECTED INFORMATION PROVIDED BY YOU 

Coach.me requires certain pieces of personal information in order to operate as designed. Requested information for use of the Services may include, but is not limited to: e-mail address, name and self-selected habits. Some of this user-provided information is optional, but a name and an active email address are required to use any of the Services. User Content you voluntarily make public using the Services will be used as described in the section entitled “User-Submitted Content” in the Terms of Service. 

ADDITIONAL COLLECTED INFORMATION 

Coach.me will also collect non-personally identifiable information. This will typically include browser or platform type, IP address, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Coach.me collects this data to best serve its users. This information will never be released to others on a personally identifiable basis, but may be released in a compiled manner. 

Coach.me may also use cookies or web beacons on the Websites to track a user’s interactions with the Services. This information will be used to deliver or optimize the Services, manage accounts, for research and analysis, to communicate with users and to develop content. You can opt-out of cookies by utilizing the settings provided in their browsers, but some of the functionality of the Services may be disabled or inaccessible if you do so. 

Additionally, Coach.me collects information from its mobile application users who have installed the Coach.me application in a similar manner to optimize the mobile experience. Any entries made on the mobile application will be used to optimize the Services, manage accounts, for research and analysis, to communicate with users and to develop content. This information will never be released to others on a personally identifiable basis, but may be released in a compiled manner. 

USE OF COLLECTED INFORMATION 

Coach.me believes that the privacy of its users is paramount and strives to use their data only in ways outlined in this Privacy Policy. Most uses of data are for internal purposes only. Coach.me may occasionally inform users of new releases and features via any communication method you have provided to Coach.me. 

**Third Parties:** Coach.me may engage certain service providers for additional features (i.e. hosting, etc.). Coach.me will thoroughly examine the privacy policies of partners to ensure that its users’ data is safe and taken care of responsibly. Third parties will not be able to use information in ways that are prohibited by the Coach.me Privacy Policy. However, Coach.me is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices of such third parties. 

**Partners:** Coach.me may partner with advertising or other partners to provide users with targeted and useful contextual advertisements or related services. These partners may set cookies which enable them to recognize your computer and compile information about you or others who use your computer. Ad networks often use this information to better target advertisements that they think will be of use to you. Coach.me’s Privacy Policy solely governs the use of information and cookies set by the Services and not by any third-party advertising partners. 

**Transfers:** Coach.me may share data internally with its affiliate companies and may disclose certain information in the event that it is merged, acquired, sold, or some of its assets are acquired. If, in Coach.me’s discretion, your information will be handled in a materially different manner than it was by Coach.me, you may have the opportunity to opt-out of having your information shared with any acquirer. 

**Law Enforcement:** Coach.me will cooperate with law enforcement and disclose any requested information if they believe, in good faith, that such disclosure is necessary to: (i) handle fraud, attacks against our systems, or security conflicts, (ii) remain in line with currently applicable state and federal laws or regulations, (iii) continue to abide by our Terms of Service, or (iv) protect the public or Coach.me from any attacks against intellectual or physical property rights. 

YOUR RESPONSIBILITY ONLINE 

Coach.me places a premium on protecting your information and uses reasonable measures including encrypted information to protect your information, but you should remain aware that any information you share online can be accessed by others. Coach.me is not responsible for the actions of those who obtain your content in this manner. Coach.me cannot guarantee your safety and security and you should be aware that submitting any information and using the Services is done at your own risk. 

MANAGING YOUR PRIVACY 

You can correct or delete your account information on the Websites and Coach.me’s applications or by e-mail _privacy [at] coach [dot] me_ , which you may also access for further assistance and questions regarding the Privacy Policy or for a copy of your account data. If you cancel your account, Coach.me will take reasonable measures to make your account information inaccessible and will limit its access to personally identifiable data to perform what is requested by you. 

JURISDICTION 

All information passed through Coach.me is primarily handled in the United States but may from time to time be handled in any country in which Coach.me or its affiliate companies maintain facilities. By using the Services, you agree that the handling of your personal information and any communication through the Services, will be governed by the laws of the United States and any applicable state laws. 

CHANGES TO THE PRIVACY POLICY 

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Coach.me may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Coach.me’s sole discretion. Coach.me encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the Services after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change. 

© 2015 Lift Worldwide, Inc. 

Loading...
